# HRISTIYAN

07367186797

ANCHEV

m hristiyan-anchev.github.io

Manchester, UK

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Young and enthusiastic person driven by curiosity and challenges on the road to knowledge.

Friendly and reliable hard working individual with experience in busy office, remote technical assistance, retail environment and customer service.

Interests in information technologies and excellent computer/digital literacy. Aiming to consistently leverage my knowledge and experience in the

effort to serve in the business' best interest.

## SKILLS

Attention to details Microsoft office suite/O365/Libre office

Prioritization and organization Digital enterprise workflow tools.

Communication/Collaboration Data Presentation/Reporting

Dedication High level of accuracy Self-motivation MS Windows / Linux

Team-minded Positive attitude

## **EMPLOYMENT**

HISTORY

**Training Lead** 

L E O N Restaurants

Mar 2019 - Present

#### Job Duties

- •Training champions act as mentors and guides in the restaurant. They impart their knowledge and experience to crew members, many of whom may be holding their first jobs.
- Explain principles behind and reasons for restaurant policies, procedures, brand and menus.
- •Demonstrate preparation of new menu items.
- •Evaluate and offer feedback on crew member performance.
- Advise managers or supervisors of problems with performance of crew members.

## **Incident Lifecycle** Coordinator

Modis

Aug 2018 - Mar 2019

## Job Duties

- •Reinforcing the incident management process established with the customer.
- Minimize business impact for the end-user.
- Improve customer satisfaction.
- Priority incidents coordination.
- Dedicated coordination and management of capabilities and ensure the right parties are aligned during the issue.
- Lead incidents until root cause/resolution or workaround is found.
- Interaction between client and the team for faster response time and and resolution time respectively.
- Directing communication channels and early engagement for any reported issue.

Barista	Pret A Manger	Apr 2017 - Mar 2018

#### Job Duties

- Promotes coffee consumption by educating customers and selling coffee, as well as preparing and serving a variety of drinks
- Welcomes customers by determining their coffee interests and needs.
- Educates customers by presenting and explaining the coffee drink menu.
- Generates revenues by attracting new customers.
- Keeps equipment operating by following operating. instructions; troubleshooting breakdowns; maintaining supplies performing preventive maintenance.
- Updates job knowledge by participating in educational opportunities.

<b>Customer Advisor</b>	Program Consult "GP"	Jan 2016 – Apr 2016
-------------------------	----------------------	---------------------

## Job duties

- Working with customers over the phone or e-mail to identify. problems with hardware or software, ordering and shipping spare parts.
- Refer difficult cases to a senior analyst or support tech.
- Scheduling visits to customers who require a technician for either resolving problems or warranty service/maintenance of equipment.
- Ordering spare parts by customers' demand.
- Filling in proforma invoices, warranty cards and maintenance reports.

<b>Bartender</b> Happy Bar&Grill Apr 2014 - Jan 2016	
--	--

# Job duties

- Preparing alcoholic or non-alcoholic beverages.
- Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving snacks and drinks.
- Determine customers' needs and preferences and make recommendations.

# **EDUCATION**

Programming Fundamentals	Software University Bulgaria	Ongoing
Information Technologies in the Business	"Angel Kanchev" University of Ruse	2014 - 2017
Mathematics and science	"Vasil Levski" High School	2001 - 2013